https://www.strengthenoursisters.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Strengthen Our Sisters at https://www.strengthenoursisters.org. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and SharingWe are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.
Strengthen Our Sisters is committed to honoring our donors’ privacy. We do not rent, sell or exchange donor names with others. A donor’s information is recorded to keep the donor informed about Strengthen Our Sisters and provide the donor an opportunity to support our programs.
Strengthen Our Sisters does not collect personal information about visitors to our website, except when visitors specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. When giving an online donation your personal information will be used by Strengthen Our Sisters and the payment processor to securely process any donations.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your name with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about new services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:• See what data we have about you, if any.• Change/correct any data we have about you.• Have us delete any data we have about you.• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information.
LinksThis web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
© 2020 Copyright
973-831-6156 • info@strengthenoursisters.org
